Hello friends, in this video I am going to tell you
how to download ICICI Lombard General Insurance policy,
so first of all
you should go to Google Play Store,
after going to Google Play Store, type ICICI Lombard
General Insurance app, then see here it is called
Care Insurance app, okay,
install this app, okay,
after installing it,
access it,
when your app is installed, then you will
see it like this, you keep scrolling and clicking next, keep clicking next, after that the
option of continue is visible, click continue,
okay, continue is visible, click continue, after continuing, enter the mobile number,
after entering the mobile
number here,
proceed further, okay,
see this, you entered the mobile number, after that
you see, they are asking for your first name here, so
here the first of your name is
Mukesh Kumar Sinha, write Mukesh from here, after that write
Kumar here, after that write Sinha here, after that
enter the date of birth and
after that enter the email ID,
after entering the email ID, you have to tick this,
you have to tick this also, then here
Proceed, okay, let's proceed and see,
after that you will see that you will
get another tip, you have to enter this OTP here
and after entering it, verify it,
okay,
now see here, your app has been downloaded,
now you can see many options in it,
see, Health Insurance is also visible,
Motor Insulin is visible, Travel
Insurance is visible and Home Insurance is
visible, okay, so whatever
policy you want to download, you will
tick it, okay, so for example, if I want to
download Motor Policy, then I
tick Motor Policy here,
Waterfalls, okay, I tick Moto Positive,
and after ticking it, let's
move ahead, okay, see this, I tick it,
after ticking, see what you see,
policy number here, if you
know the policy number, then enter the policy number, if you do
n't know the policy number, then enter the vehicle number
and you have to enter the last five digits of the chassis of the vehicle number
here, okay,
after that what do you have to do, you have to add a Motor Policy,
okay, if you enter a Motor Policy, then
your Motor Policy will be added, then let's
explain further by doing it first  Let's see, if
you don't know the policy number,
what will you enter? You need the vehicle number, let's look at the vehicle number
and add it.
Okay
[Music]
Now, enter the vehicle number like this.
After entering the vehicle number, you have to enter the chassis number in all 5
digits. After entering the 5 digits, you have to
add the Add Motor Policy as you see here. Okay
[Music]
When you add it,
you will see it like this. Okay,
you will see Bahujan. After that, to view its details,
you will go back a little bit. Okay,
when you update it, when you add it,
look in your motor policy. Here you have to
view 180 and download it.
You will have to go here. Okay, so let's go there.
Okay,
when you open it, you will see the
policy number, LED TV, policy holder's
name, registration number, vehicle
model option like this. Also,
you can see the policy details here. Okay, as soon as
you click on it, your policy will be
automatically downloaded. In this way,
you
can also download the policy and view it.
If there is any  If you have a pen, you
can go here and claim it,
okay, through details, so like our video as much as possible
and subscribe to the channel
and share it, thank you.